http://www.sqm.ca/index.php/en/privacy.html

Friday, December 11 2020
English
English
French
HomeCorporate ProfileAbout SQMVision, Mission, and Core ValuesOur LogoBest Mystery Shopping Company in TorontoScams and Fraud WarningsSQM is a Green Company!Corporate Social ResponsibilityWeb-based ReportingCase StudySQM in the MediaIncreasing ROIStaff TrainingMedia ArchiveBloggers Who Love SQM!Programs and ServicesInspection ServicesMystery Shopping ProgramsBrand Experience EvaluationsLoss Prevention Mystery Shop ProgramsCompetitive Analysis ProgramsIntegrity InspectionsHuman Resources AuditsKitchen AuditsMerchandising AuditsThird Party AuditsSupplier Value Added Mystery Shop ProgramsFactory AuditsPhysical Inventory CountsSecurity AuditsCompetitive Price ChecksCustomer CountsSQM's Anti Counterfeiting / Grey Market Monitoring ProgramTrust AuditsRisk Management ServicesMarket ResearchComment Card ProgramsOnline Feedback ProgramsTelephone SurveysIn-Person SurveysCustomer Exit InterviewsMail-In SurveysOnline Focus GroupsFocus GroupsRap SessionsInternal Feedback ProgramsField ServicesField Merchandising & Field Marketing ServicesLeasing Our TechnologySQM DirectBusiness SupportSales BlitzesMarketing ProjectsPromotional ProjectsSQM VideosSQM Picks
Last Updated: June 2018
Sensors Quality Management Inc. Privacy Policy
Over the years, there has been a lot of development in the area of privacy, data protection, and more specifically the collection, use, and protection of personal information. In January of 2004, The Privacy Commissioner of Canada released the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act often referred to as PIPEDA. In May 2018, the European Union introduced into law the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). While each of these are unique in some ways, for the most part these regulations place the focus on commercial operators to address the collection, care, handling, processing and security of personal data. These initiatives are not only laws that govern commercial organizations with regards to personal data, but they have set in place good handling practices to essentially protect any personal data that they collect.
Since Sensors Quality Management Inc. (SQM) first started collecting personal data, we have always been concerned with the collection, handling and protection of this information. Within this document we would like to remove any mystery associated with what we collect, why we collect information, how we process, and the procedures in place to protect the data.
SQM is committed to following the obligations, guidelines and expectations of these initiatives. We are completely transparent about how personal data is handled, while protecting the privacy and security of personal information we collect and hold.
The Principles of Data Protection
Under most legislation associated with personal data, including the new GDPR, there are generally six different expectations that SQM is required to comply with. They are:
Personal data is to be processed in a transparent, fair and lawful manner.
Personal data is to be collected only for legitimate purposes for which it was clearly explained. It is not to be used in any manner that is not aligned with the initial purpose.
The data collected is to be adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in the relationship and only to those purposes.
Personal data should be accurate and maintained up-to-date.
Personal data should be held for a period no longer than necessary to the original purpose.
Data security processes and procedures are to be in place to ensure the security of all personal data held by SQM.
SQM Privacy Statement
At Sensors Quality Management Inc., the privacy and protection of your personal information is of paramount importance. We do not share, sell, provide, lend or otherwise transmit personal data to anyone or any group outside of our organization.
Public: All pages on the SQM public website are free to navigate without the requirement to provide any personal information. The web hosting systems used by SQM do collect and retain a log of the domains that visited our website, however, this information is only used for security purposes. Logs are never used for any marketing, advertising, or purposes other than the maintenance of a secure system.
For additional details on Sensors Quality Management Inc., and our policies on data privacy, please select from the options below
If you are a Client (Clients Privacy Policy)
If you are a member of our Field Force (Field Force Privacy Policy)
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small file that a website or service provider transfers to your computer when you access that system using a web browser. This file then permits the site or service provider to recognize you and even capture and/or retain certain attribute type information.
On the public non password protected side of our website, we do not use cookies. On our password protected, private side of our websites, we do use cookies. These are used to enhance the user experience or as a convenience (i.e. the setting of language preferences. Once the language has been set, the cookie helps by recognizing that setting on subsequent visits.).
Cookies are not used on the SQM website for any other purpose. No personal or user behaviour type information is collected or shared with others.
Tags: Privacy Policy, Legal Statement
Print
Email
English
English
French
HomeCorporate ProfileAbout SQMVision, Mission, and Core ValuesOur LogoBest Mystery Shopping Company in TorontoScams and Fraud WarningsSQM is a Green Company!Corporate Social ResponsibilityWeb-based ReportingCase StudySQM in the MediaIncreasing ROIStaff TrainingMedia ArchiveBloggers Who Love SQM!Programs and ServicesInspection ServicesMystery Shopping ProgramsBrand Experience EvaluationsLoss Prevention Mystery Shop ProgramsCompetitive Analysis ProgramsIntegrity InspectionsHuman Resources AuditsKitchen AuditsMerchandising AuditsThird Party AuditsSupplier Value Added Mystery Shop ProgramsFactory AuditsPhysical Inventory CountsSecurity AuditsCompetitive Price ChecksCustomer CountsSQM's Anti Counterfeiting / Grey Market Monitoring ProgramTrust AuditsRisk Management ServicesMarket ResearchComment Card ProgramsOnline Feedback ProgramsTelephone SurveysIn-Person SurveysCustomer Exit InterviewsMail-In SurveysOnline Focus GroupsFocus GroupsRap SessionsInternal Feedback ProgramsField ServicesField Merchandising & Field Marketing ServicesLeasing Our TechnologySQM DirectBusiness SupportSales BlitzesMarketing ProjectsPromotional ProjectsSQM VideosSQM Picks
